here are the stories were covering this
これはこれ を カバーしていた物語です
week in the category 5 TV newsroom
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルームでの週
Lubuntu is dropping the 32 bit high so
Lubuntu は32ビットを高く落としている
unfortunately some people still use
残念ながら何人かの人々はまだ使用しています
Internet Explorer and yet another
Internet Explorerとさらに別の
serious exploit has been found
深刻な悪用が発見されました
Dyson plans to release a radical
ダイソンは過激派を解放する計画
electric car in 2020 and equifax teens
2020年の電気自動車と equifax 10代
have a grasp on security these stories
これらの物語の安全性を把握している
are coming right up don't go anywhere
すぐに 来ている どこにも行かないでください
whether you shop on ThinkGeek gearbest
ThinkGeekギアベストで買い物をするかどうか
B&amp;H photo video eBay or Amazon or even
B&amp;Hの写真ビデオのeBayやAmazon、さらには
if you want a free trial of audible
あなたが聞こえるの無料試用版が欲しいなら
you'll find the best deals and support
あなたは最高のお得な情報やサポートを見つけることができます
the shows we produce by simply visiting
我々が単に訪れることによって作り出すショー
the shopping sites you already frequent
あなたがすでに 頻繁に訪れる ショッピングサイト
by using the links on our website visit
私達のウェブサイトの訪問のリンクを使用して
category 5 TV slash partners for the
のカテゴリ 5 TV スラッシュパートナー
full and ever-growing list and help us
常に増え続けているリスト
create more free content like this show
この番組のように 無料でコンテンツを作成する
thank you for shopping with our partners
私たちのパートナーと一緒に買い物をしてくれてありがとう
and thank you for watching this is the
これを見てくれてありがとう
category 5 TV newsroom covering the
カバー カテゴリ5のテレビ ニュース編集室
week's top tech stories with a slight
ちょっとした週のトップテックストーリー
Linux box if you are hoping to download
ダウンロードしたい 場合はLinuxボックス
a boon to 17 point 10 32-bit come its
17ポイント10 32ビットへの恩恵
release next month we've got some bad
来月リリースします
news to give you a boon to is dropping
あなたに恩恵を与えるためのニュースはドロップされています
32-bit builds of a boon to desktop
デスクトップへの恩恵の32ビットビルド
entirely as of a boon to 17 point 10
完全に17ポイント10への恩恵のように
Canonical's dimitri john LED cove has
Canonicalのdimitri john LEDコーブは持っています
asked the boon to release team to action
チームに行動を起こすようブーンに頼みました
a proposal he put forth earlier in the
彼が前に出した提案
development cycle in which he argued
彼が主張 した開発サイクル
that the i30 i386 builds of a boon to
i30 i386は次のような利点があります
desktop ok 32-bit builds should no
デスクトップOK 32ビットビルドは不可
longer be produced no changes are being
変更はされていません
made to other builds of ubuntu 17 point
ubuntu 17点の他のビルドに作られた
10 such as minimal install ISOs or the
最小インストールISOなどの10
net install option and this news does
ネットインストールオプションとこのニュースは
not mean a boon to won't run on 32-bit
32ビットで動作しないという恩恵を意味するのではありません
simply that you won't be able to
あなたがすることはできませんことを単に
download a premade desktop ISO image for
の デスクトップISOイメージを ダウンロードし てください。
it the 32-bit a boon to archive is not
32ビットのアーカイブが功を奏しているのではない
going anywhere either
どちらかに行く
if you're currently running a 32-bit
現在32ビットを実行している場合
version of Ubuntu you can continue to
あなたが続けることができるUbuntuのバージョン
upgrade to new room
新しい部屋に アップグレード する
as normal this change also does not
通常どおり、この変更もしません
affect the boon to flavors such as x/z
x / zの ような味への恩恵に影響を与える
boon to Ubuntu Matei a boon to budgie
Ubuntu Mateiへ のブーン、仲間へのブーン
and at all they'll be free to make their
そして、まったく 彼らは 自由に彼らを作る ことができるでしょう
own decisions about what they support
彼らが支持するもの についての自身の決定
and there's always a point to 16 point O
常に16点 O までのポイントがあります
for LTS which is supported until 2021
2021年までサポートされているLTS用
and readily available as a 32-bit image
そして 32ビット画像として すぐに 利用可能
here's a question I have yeah who would
ここに私が持っている質問があります
want to download you know the whole
あなたは全体を知ってダウンロードしたいです
32-bit versus 64-bit argument the 32-bit
32ビット対64ビットの引数32ビット
kernel is anything up until three three
カーネルは3から3まで何でも
and a half gigs of RAM you refined to
そして あなたが 改良した RAMの半分のギグ
run a 32-bit OS there was a time years
32年前に32ビットOSを走らせる
ago when it was really hard to get a
手に入れるのが本当に難しかった 前に
64-bit OS hey but what does it mean it
64ビットOS ちょっとでもそれは どういう意味 ですか
means that you your computer can run
あなたのコンピュータ は 実行 できるということです
faster it means it can do more
より速くそれはより多くのことができることを意味します
operations at any given time it means
いつでも操作
that you can have more RAM like we're
私たちのように あなた はもっと多くの RAM を 持つ こと ができること
putting 32 gigs of RAM in a computer for
32ギグのRAMをコンピュータに入れる
you and that could not happen on a
あなたとそれがで起こることができませんでした
32-bit operating system ok it has to be
32ビットオペレーティングシステムは 大丈夫 です
64-bit so what's this hole a boon to
64ビットな ので、この 穴は 何に 役立つのか
thing a boon to of course is a flavor of
もちろん恩恵を受けるものはの風味です
Linux Linux is an alternative to
Linux Linuxは、に代わるものです。
Microsoft Windows it's an alternative to
Microsoft Windowsはそれに代わるものです
Mac OS and it is a free operating system
Mac OSとそれは無料のオペレーティングシステムです
for your computer so thanks to that
お使いの コンピュータの ためにそれのおかげで
you've got bleeding edge technology and
あなたは、 最先端の技術を 持っている と 出血
now they're saying hey here's our free
今、彼らはちょっとここに私たちの無料だと言っている
OS and we're keeping up with the times
OSと私たちは時代についていく
we're dropping the 32-bit ISO which is
我々は32ビットISO を落としています
the downloadable disc that you can
ダウンロード可能なディスク のことができます。
install on your computer right and
コンピュータに正しくインストールして
instead we're pushing you to have to
代わりに、私たちはあなたにやらなければならないように促しています
install the 64-bit so that means no more
64ビットをインストールしてください。
older hardware that doesn't support
サポートしていない古いハードウェア
64-bit because when you say I 386 32-bit
64ビットなので、386 32ビットと言うと
those are the old computers so if you've
あなたがきた ので、 もしそれらは古いコンピュータです
got an old 40 60 X 2 you're not going to
あなたがする つもり はない 古い40 60 X 2を持っている
be able to install from the ISO ubuntu
ISO ubuntu からインストールできるようにする
any longer because it's passe it's old
もうパスだから古い
technology 64-bit is the way to go and
64ビットテクノロジが最善の方法です。
that's what they're pushing for but good
それは彼らが推進しているものだが良い
note that if you already have 32-bit
32ビットをすでにお持ちの場合
Linux installed you can upgrade right
Linuxがインストールされているのでアップグレードできます
yet the latest and greatest you just
まだ最新かつ最高の あなた だけ
have to you have to get the Installer
インストーラーを入手する必要があります
from the older
年上から
version and then upgrade from there
バージョンしてからそこからアップグレード
right fine
まあまあ
that's alright cuz you already have it
それは大丈夫です、あなたはすでにそれを持っています
so you're ok if you're curious about it
それであなたが それについて興味があるならば大丈夫です
boom - if you're curious about Linux hey
ブーム - もしあなたがLinuxに興味があれば
get on to our website category 5 TV
私達のウェブサイトのカテゴリ 5 TVに乗りなさい
click on contact us there's a way to
お問い合わせをクリックしてください。
actually reach out to the show we'd love
実際に私たちが愛したいショーに手を差し伸べる
to field your questions excellent thank
あなたの 質問に答えて くれてありがとう
you I'll just kind of slide over here to
あなたは私が ここに ちょうどスライドのようなものになります
be the best until I need it again
もう一度必要になるまで 最善を尽くし なさい
there's a bug in the most current
最新のバグがあります
version of Internet Explorer that leaks
リークする Internet Explorerのバージョン
the addresses search search terms or any
アドレス検索検索語または任意の
other text typed into the address bar
アドレスバーに 入力された他のテキスト
the bug allows any currently visited
このバグは現在訪れている人をすべて許可します
website to view any text entered into
入力したテキストを表示するWebサイト
the address bar as soon as the user hits
ユーザーがヒットしたらすぐにアドレスバー
enter the technique can expose sensitive
テクニックを入力して敏感にさらすことができます
information a user didn't intend to be
情報利用者があることを意図していませんでした
viewed by remote websites including the
含むリモートWebサイトで閲覧
web addresses address the user is about
ユーザーの Webアドレスaddress
to visit the hack can also expose search
ハックを訪問することも検索を公開することができます
queries
問い合わせ
since ie allows them to be typed into
つまり、それらを入力することを可能にします
the address bar and then retrieved from
アドレスバーを 取得してから取得
Bing or other search services this
Bingまたは他の検索サービスこれ
weakness
弱点
may allow malicious sites to view
悪意のあるサイトによる閲覧を許可する可能性があります。
information the user presumes was
ユーザーが推測した情報
private people should strongly consider
民間人は強く考慮すべきです
using google chrome months Mozilla
Googleクローム月間 Mozillaを使用して
Firefox or another 9 non-iea hour that's
Firefox や だ もう一つの 9非IEA時間
a huge scary deal goes without saying at
巨大な恐ろしい取引はで言うまでもないです
this point don't use internet explorer
この時点では インターネットエクスプローラを 使用 しないでください
if you bring up that e that blue e any
あなたがそのe を 育てれ ば その 青いe any
longer if that's what you're using to
それがあなたが今 使って いるものであればもっと長く
surf the web you're doing it wrong
あなたがそれを間違ってやっているウェブをサーフィンする
please listen to me when I say start
私が言う時は私の言うことを聞いてください
using Chrome start using Firefox start
Firefoxの起動を使用して クロムの開始を使用して
using a more modern browser internet
最新のブラウザインターネットを使用する
internet explorer is done right and like
インターネット エクスプローラが正しく行われているようです
windows XP it's not safe to use anymore
Windows XPそれ は もう 使用する のは安全で はあり ません
some would say ever was right now so do
今は今だったと言う人もいるでしょう
they do they try and push themselves or
彼らは自分たちでやろうとするか
are they just a default sorta do they
それらは単なるデフォルトの 問題ですか。
realize the users yeah well does it come
ユーザーは、 ええ 、それは 良く 来る ん実現
free does it come pre-loaded on
無料でプリロードされていますか
computers Internet Explorer older
Internet Explorerより古いコンピュータ
computers yes ok Windows 7 had Internet
コンピュータはいOK Windows 7は インターネットを 持っていました
Explorer pre-installed right wrong
エクスプローラプリインストール 善悪
Windows 10 it comes with a program
Windows 10にはプログラムが付属しています
called edge Microsoft edge which is
マイクロソフトエッジと呼ばれる
their replacement for Internet Explorer
Internet Explorerに代わるもの
but still I would lean toward Chrome
それでも私は Chromeに 傾くだろう
would probably be my suggestion and
おそらく私の提案だろう
there are reasons for that beyond it's
それを超える 理由があります
not a brand war it's nothing like that
ブランド戦争ではない
other than from Microsoft's perspective
Microsoftの視点以外から
Microsoft wants you to use only their
マイクロソフトはあなたが彼らだけを使用することを望んでいる
software if they could have it their way
彼らはそれを彼らの方法で持つことができればソフトウェア
that's how it would be but the other
それはそれは可能だろうかだが、他の
products that are out there are simply
そこに いる製品は、単純です
more current more safe more
もっともっともっと安全にもっともっと
bleeding-edge and you know a lot of any
最先端で、あなたはたくさんのことを知っています
piece of software can have exploits any
ソフトウェアの一部に悪用が 可能
piece of software be it edged Chrome
クロームエッジのソフトウェア
Firefox Internet Explorer can have these
Firefox Internet Explorerはこれらを持つことができます
kinds of problems but the fact is chrome
問題の種類が、事実は クロムです
is bringing out this is a Google owned
これを出しているのはGoogleが所有している
product is bringing out a new version
製品は新しいバージョンを出しています
all the time any time there's an exploit
常に悪用されている
found they're fixing it right now on the
彼らは今それを直している
other side of this is Internet Explorer
これの反対側はInternet Explorerです
this is from Microsoft if I could say
私が言うことができれば これ はマイクロソフトから です
Internet Internet Explorer this is no
Internet Internet Explorerこれはノーです
longer supported ok like Windows XP as
Windows XPの ようにサポートされています
exploits come out as things are
悪用は物事があるように出てくる
discovered like this the problem will
このようにして発見された問題 は
remain for all time so if you continue
あなたが 続けるので あれば 、 ずっと残り続ける
using that product you are no longer
その製品 を使用してあなたは もうい ない
going to be safe against that particular
その特定に対して安全になるだろう
threat now this one's a bad one you
今脅威これはあなたにとって悪いものです
consider yeah if you're on a web site
あなたが Webサイトにアクセス している場合は、ええを検討してください
and then you start typing something into
それから 何かをタイプし始めます
the address bar which you think is your
あなたが 思う アドレスバー はあなたのものです
search engine or going to another web
検索エンジンまたは別の ウェブに 行く
site if you're if you're on this
あなたがこれをやっ て いるならあなたが サイト なら
malicious web site and you enter
悪意のあるWebサイトを 入力して
category 5 TV in the address bar it will
アドレスバーにカテゴリ5のテレビが表示されます
know that you have now gone to category
あなたが今 カテゴリに 行ったことを知っている
5 TV normally that information is not
5テレビ通常その情報ではありません
shared with the website frights which
ウェブサイト と共有
can be an issue if you're doing things
あなたが物事をやっているなら問題になることができます
like a private search I don't know
プライベート検索のように私は知らない
really what you could do in your address
あなたの住所で本当にできること
bar that would be Oberer private I mean
Obererプライベートに なるバー
oh I went to Facebook oh I went to
ああ私はFacebookに行きました ああ私はに行きました
Google but still you know yeah you want
グーグルがそれでもあなたはあなたが望むことを知っている
to know that your stuff is secure and
あなたのものが安全であることを知る ために
it's not when you're using Internet
インターネットを使用しているときではありません
Explorer this particular exploit too
この悪用 も 探検する
because now we think about exploited
今、私たちは悪用について考える
websites are vulnerable to collecting
Webサイトは収集に対して脆弱です
this data right and so you think well
このデータは正しい ので、よく考えています
who would do that why would I be on a
誰がそれをするだろうなぜ私は
website that is malicious I don't go to
悪意のある Webサイトにアクセス しない
those kinds of websites you
そのような種類の ウェブサイトあなた
I'd say the fact is here's how hackers
事実はここにあるハッカー
do it how Fisher's do it and these kinds
フィッシャーのやり方とこれらの種類のやり方
of things they buy ad space right you
彼らがあなたに合った広告スペースを買うもの
might be on Yahoo you might be on
Yahooにいるかもしれません
Facebook and you are being served ads
Facebookとあなたは広告を配信されています
right and these people who are selling
正しいそして売っているこれらの人々
advertisements may not catch that the
広告はそれをキャッチすることはできません
particular advertisement that they are
彼らがいる特定の広告
hosting is malicious I saw one on Yahoo
ホスティングは悪意のある 私がYahooで見たものです
that was installing malware directly on
それは直接 マルウェアをインストール していました
people's computers because it was an
それがだったので人々のコンピュータ
infected flash object that was
感染したFlashオブジェクト
installing this malware on Internet
このマルウェアをインターネットにインストールする
Explorer driven computers so this kind
エクスプローラー駆動のコンピューターな のでこのようなもの
of stuff happens hackers know that hey
もののハッカーはちょっとということを知って 起こります
III may not be able to get you to come
III は あなたに 来 てもらうこと が でき ないかもしれません
to my website but I can put my code on a
私のウェブサイト への が、私は上の私のコードを置くことができます
particular popular website that I know
私が知っている特定の人気のあるウェブサイト
you're going to frequent scary stuff can
あなたは頻繁に怖いものにするつもりです
be so don't use Explorer which the
エクスプローラを 使わない でください。
chrome switch to firefox anything but IE
Firefox以外のFirefoxへのクロムスイッチ
ran that explorer i have a fun news
その 探検家を 走った 私は楽しい ニュースがある
story yes they're all fun this one's
物語はい彼らはすべて これが 楽しいです
less scary maybe less conspiracy
それほど怖い多分 少ない陰謀
theories moving forward yes Dyson the
理論は前進している
engineering company best known for its
そのために最もよく知られているエンジニアリング会社
vacuum cleaners and fans plans to spend
掃除 機やファンが過ごす予定
two billion pounds developing a radical
急進的な 20億ポンドの 開発
electric car the battery powered vehicle
電気自動車バッテリー駆動自動車
is due to be launched in 2020 Dyson says
2020年に発売される予定です
400 staff have been working on the
400人のスタッフが
secret project for the past two years
過去2年間 のための秘密のプロジェクト
its headquarters in Wiltshire however
ウィルトシャー州に本社しかし、
the cards is not yet exists with no
カードはまだ存在していません
prototype belt and a factory set is yet
プロトタイプベルトと工場セットはまだ
to be chosen Sir James declined to give
ジェームズ卿は与えることを拒んだ
further details of the project with only
だけで プロジェクトの詳細
the only leaked information being an
唯一の漏洩情報は
internal email or email where he simply
社内のEメール、または彼が単に行ったEメール
states competition for the new
州は新しい競争
technology in the automat automotive
オートマット 自動車の 技術
industry is fierce and we must do
産業は熾烈であり、我々はやらなければならない
everything we can to keep the specifics
詳細を守るためにできることすべて
of our vehicle confidential okay this is
私たちの車の機密の大丈夫これは大丈夫です
why it's exciting to me okay because
なぜそれが私にはわくわくするようなわくわくする 理由
it's out of left field
それは 左のフィールドの外に あります
Dyson they might
ダイソン
do you make vacuum cleaners it kind of
あなたは それが種類の 掃除 機 を作りますか
may they babble in tech and stuff I love
彼らは 私が愛している 技術や ものに 戸惑い ますか
it I I just for something I I know that
それは私が 私が 知っていること だけのため に 私 は
there are a bunch of companies out there
そこにたくさん の 会社があります
that are really focusing on these cars
それは 本当に これらの車に 焦点を合わせ ています
and I get it but Dyson it just blows me
そして私はそれを手に入れるがダイソンそれはただ私を吹く
away I'm gonna do something interesting
離れて私は面白いことをやるつもりだ
now here's where I wish I had artistic
今ここに私は私が芸術的だったことを望むところです
abilities yeah and maybe here's your
能力ええそして多分これはあなたのものです
challenge this week my friends come up
私の友人が来今週の挑戦
with a concept car that Dyson might
ダイソンがコンセプトカーとして
create I'm picturing probably powered by
私はおそらく描いている
a tornado a black hole they have that's
彼らが持っている竜巻ブラックホール
wiffle ball things yeah it's gonna be
wiffle ball things そうだよ
wild I want to see your caricatures of
あなたの似顔絵を見たい
this car I love this idea it's it's
この車私はそれはそれはだだこのアイデアを愛し
going to it's probably gonna be the
それに行くことでしょつもり です
best-selling car of 2020 this is the
2020年のベストセラー車はこれです
strangest leak ever though when you
あなたがいたときにも変なリーク
think about it yeah we're bringing out a
考えてみましょう
car but not telling you anything about
車だけど何も言わないで
it well also they don't they don't have
それは彼らも 持っ ていませ ん
a prototype
プロトタイプ
they don't have working on it for two
彼らは2つのためにそれに取り組んでいません
years we've been working on it for two
私達は2年間それに取り組んできました
years we're not telling you anything
年私たちはあなたに 何も 言っていない
about it it's top secret and we don't
それは それが 最高の 秘密であり、私たちはしません
have anything we don't have a location
場所がないものがある
it's gonna be built
それは造られるつもりです
yeah we don't but we know how much money
ええ、そうではありません が、いくらお金を知っています
we're gonna spend on it in other words
言い換えれば、私たちはそれに費やすつもりです
two years ago they were sitting around
2年前、彼らは座ってい ました
having a glass of wine and said we've
ワイングラスを片手に
been doing this for two years maybe it's
2 年間 のためにこれをやって、多分 それはです
a streetsweeper
通り掃除人
weird back yeah it'll clean the streets
奇妙なバックええそれは通りをきれいにします
maybe it'll scrub the air why they can't
彼らができない理由は多分それは空気をこすります
say anything because I robots are gonna
私のロボットはつもりだから何でも言う
sue them for the idea I'll do anything
私は何でもするという考えで彼らを訴える
that represents or resembles a Roomba
それはルンバを表すかそれに似ています
how great would it be cleaning the
それはどのくらいきれいになるでしょう
streets the dicing car nice in failing
失敗するのにいい ダイシングカー
to correctly patch a known vulnerability
既知の脆弱性を正しく修正するため
and exposing the personal data of
の個人 データを 公開する
potentially 143 million Americans to
潜在的に1億4300万人のアメリカ人
hackers Oh Equifax made a security
Oh Equifax がセキュリティを確保したハッカー
blunder of epic proportions however it
壮大なスケール の失態 しかし、それ
appears the company is just getting star
会社はただスターになっているようです
leaving its digital doors wide open to
デジタルドアを広く開放する
criminals apparently wasn't enough for
犯罪者は明らかに十分ではなかった
the credit reporting agency as it's now
現在の信用報告機関
sending hack victims directly into the
ハックの被害者を
open arms of unknown internet pranksters
未知のインターネットいたずらのオープン腕
yes Equifax is directing those concerned
はいEquifaxは関係者に指示しています
about the data breach and its
データ侵害とその
repercussions to a fake website set up
偽のWebサイトの設定への 影響
to troll the company itself that's right
会社自体を荒らすことは 正しい
the official Equifax Twitter account is
公式のEquifax Twitterアカウントは
pointing people to what looks to be a
aに見えるものに人々 を 向ける
fake site okay a phishing site Equifax
偽のサイト大丈夫 フィッシングサイトEquifax
created a very real site WWE Koufax
非常に現実的なサイト WWE Koufaxを作成しました
security where people can enter their
人々が入ることができるセキュリティ
last name along with the last six digits
最後の6 桁とともに姓
of their social security number to see
社会保障番号を見る
if they were affected by the hack
ハッキングの影響を受けた場合
unsurprisingly someone cloned that site
当然のことながら、誰かがそのサイトを複製した
and hosted a copy at a very similar URL
そして非常によく似たURLでコピーをホストしました
which is www.securityasi.com or so
これはwww.securityasi.comかそこら
easily confused that Equifax itself
そのEquifax自体を容易に混乱させ た
apparently can't tell the difference
明らかに違いを見分けることはできません
thankfully the maker of this boost site
ありがたいことにこの後押しサイトのメーカー
seems more interested in calling out
電話をかけることにもっと興味があるようです
Equifax for their incompetence than
彼らの無能のためのEquifaxより
stealing the personal information of
の個人情報 を 盗む
unsuspecting victims the header of the
疑う余地のない被害者
fake site reads cybersecurity incident
偽のサイトが サイバーセキュリティ インシデントを 読み取ります
and reporting customer information which
顧客情報を報告する
is totally fake
完全に偽物です
why did Equifax use a domain that is so
なぜEquifax はそのような ドメイン を使用しましたか
easily impersonated by a phishing site
フィッシングサイトに偽装されている
the spoof sir the spoof site goes on
なりすましサイトへ行くなりすまし
saying Equifax should have hosted this
Equifaxがこれを主催するべきだった
on Equifax com with a reputable SSL
信頼できるSSLと Equifax comで
certificate instead they chose an easily
証明書代わりに彼らは簡単に選んだ
impersonated domain and used a jellybean
偽装ドメインとクラゲを使用
SSL cert that any script Kitty can
任意のスクリプトキティができる SSL証明書
impersonate in 20 minutes it's not clear
20分で偽装する
if the site captures the data entered by
サイトがで入力されたデータをキャプチャした場合
tricked consumer if it discards it there
それをそこ に捨てるならば、だまされた消費者
is no real contact information on the
上の本当の連絡先情報がありません
page and many of the links take you to a
ページとリンクの多くはあなたを
YouTube video for Rick Astley's never
リック・アストリーの決して の YouTube動画
going to give you up nice okay so
あなたをあきらめて いい よ
they've pulled it off and they've
彼らはそれをやってのけ、そして彼らは
tricked people into going to this and
人々をだましてこれに行き、
equifax themselves have tweeted the
equifax自体がツイートし ています
phishing site yes it is
フィッシングサイトはい
I just it's it's funny because I don't
私はしないので、それは面白いよ
know if you notice it was like one of
あなたはそれがのようなものであることに気づいたかどうかを知っている
them was security Equifax knew everyone
彼らはセキュリティだった Equifaxは皆を知っていた
was Equifax security so I can stay just
Equifaxセキュリティでした
reversed it so it's actually like legit
それを逆にしたので、実際には合法的です
looking for the dyslexic but they're
失読症を探しているが、 彼らは
right yeah oh you sure but why would
そうそうあなたは確信しています
they ever register a domain like that
彼らは今まで その ようなドメインを登録しています
it's stupid right no I did go back over
ばかげ たことだよ
category-five TV and made sure and yes
カテゴリ5 テレビと 確かにしたとはい
we did give the correct address for you
正しい住所を教えてください
but fact is Equifax themselves gave the
しかし、事実はEquifax自身が
wrong one right hello so thankfully they
間違った右のhello ので、ありがたいことに、彼ら
they caught on and and stopped it right
彼らはつかまって正しく止めた
and thankfully the person who was
そして ありがたいことに、
responsible was just having a little bit
責任は少しだけ を 持っていました
of fun but you know who knows what the
楽しい の が 、あなたは 何を知っている人 知っています
next guy could be right exactly but
次の人はまさに正しいかもしれません が
that's all the time that we have all
それは私たち全員が持っているすべての時間です
right comments in exactly below big
すぐ下の正しいコメント
thanks this week - Roy W Nash in our
おかげで今週- 私たちの中に ロイ・W・ ナッシュ
community of viewers for submitting
投稿者のコミュニティ
stories to us this week thanks for
今週のストーリー
watching the category-5 TV newsroom
カテゴリ5のテレビ ニュース編集室を見て
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
いいねを忘れずに購読する
all your tech news with a slight Linux
ちょっとしたLinuxで あなたの すべて の技術 ニュース
bias and for more free content be sure
バイアスをかけ、より自由なコンテンツを確実に
to check out our website from the
から 当社の ウェブサイト を チェックアウト する
category-five TV newsroom I'm Sasha
category-five TVニュースルーム 私は Sasha です
Rickman
リックマン
[Music]
[音楽]
[Applause]
[拍手]
you
君は
[Music]
[音楽]